AD.MC.026
AbuDhabi
A Gulf of Images
2017
AD.MC.026
AbuDhabi
4.0 Cubic feet
Nastasi, Michele, Mr
Object AD_MC_026
- A Gulf of Images, 2017 (Object AD_MC_026_ref209)
  - View over West Bay Skyline from Museum of Islamic Art in Doha., 18 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref1)
    Architecture; Digital photographs; Doha, Qatar; Skyline; Windows
  - View from Souk Sharq in Kuwait City., 10 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref2)
    Architecture; Banners; Boats/Ships; Digital photographs; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Markets; Skyline
  - Sheikh Zayed Road from Four Points Sheraton Hotel, Dubai., 11 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref3)
    Architecture; Digital photographs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Skyline; Streets/Roads
  - View of The Opera District in Dubai., 14 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref4)
    Architecture; Digital photographs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Entertainment; Fences; Streets/Roads
  - View of Opera Store in The Opera District, Dubai., 12 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref5)
    Architecture; Digital photographs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Entertainment; Men; Workers
  - Plant souq in Olaya Streey, Riyadh., 30 March 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref6)
    Architecture; Cars; Digital photographs; Flowers; Markets; Men; Potted Plants; Riyadh, Saudi Arabia; Skyline; Streets/Roads
  - View from Al Faisaliah Tower, Riyadh., 29 March 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref7)
    Architecture; Digital photographs; Riyadh, Saudi Arabia; Skyline; Streets/Roads
  - View from Le Royal Meridien Hotel, Abu Dhabi., 29 March 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref8)
    Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Architecture; Digital photographs; Hotels; Skyline
  - View from the Crystal Tower, looking at Sharq, Kuwait City., 11 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref9)
    Architecture; Buildings; Digital photographs; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Skyline
  - Street view of road crossing in Business Bay, Dubai., 14 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref10)
    Buildings; Cars; Digital photographs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Men; Streets/Roads; Women
  - Street view of downtown Abu Dhabi at World Trade Center, Abu Dhabi., 18 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref11)
    Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Architecture; Buildings; Cars; Digital photographs; Men; Streets/Roads; Women
  - Street view at Palace Avenue, Manama., 14 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref12)
    Architecture; Buildings; Cars; Digital photographs; Manama, Bahrain; Men; Streets/Roads
  - The Gate, (Players), Abu Dhabi., 17 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref13)
    Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Architecture; Buildings; Digital photographs
  - View from the National Bank of Kuwait under construction, Kuwait City., 12 February 207; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref14)
    Architecture; Buildings; Digital photographs; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Skyline; Windows
  - View looking down from the Burj Mohammed bin Rashid, Abu Dhabi., 18 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref15)
    Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Architecture; Buildings; Digital photographs; Skyline; Water
  - Al Hamra Tower seen from the National Bank of Kuwait (under construction), Kuwait City., 12 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref16)
    Architecture; Buildings; Construction; Digital photographs; Kuwait City, Kuwait
  - View of The Opera District, Dubai., 14 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref17)
    Architecture; Buildings; Construction; Digital photographs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Workers
  - Street view of Fatima Bint Mubarak Street, Abu Dhabi., 19 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref18)
  - Street view at Palace Avenue, Manama., 14 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref19)
  - Street view of Al Khalifa Avenue, Manama., 14 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref20)
    Architecture; Buildings; Cars; Digital photographs; Manama, Bahrain; Men; Rainwater; Streets/Roads
  - Business Bay, Dubai., 13 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref21)
    Architecture; Buildings; Cars; Digital photographs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Streets/Roads; Women
  - View of Abdullah Ibn Al Arqam, Majdool Tower, Riyadh., 26 March 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref22)
    Architecture; Buildings; Cars; Construction; Digital photographs; Men; Riyadh, Saudi Arabia
  - View from Kingdom Tower, looking North, Riyadh., 29 March 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref23)
    Architecture; Buildings; Riyadh, Saudi Arabia; Skyline; Streets/Roads
  - View from Kingdom Tower, looking South, Riyadh., 28 March 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref24)
    Architecture; Buildings; Digital photographs; Riyadh, Saudi Arabia; Skyline; Streets/Roads
  - View from National Bank of Kuwait under construction, Kuwait City., 12 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref25)
    Architecture; Buildings; Construction; Digital photographs; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Skyline
  - King Fahad Road, Tamkeen Tower, Riyadh., 30 march 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref26)
    Buildings; Digital photographs; Men; Riyadh, Saudi Arabia; Trucks
  - Fruit vendor at gas station on King Fahad Road, Riyadh., 30 March 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref27)
    Cars; Construction; Digital photographs; Fruits & Vegetables; Men; Riyadh, Saudi Arabia; Skyline
  - Street view of Business Bay, Riyadh., 30 March 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref28)
    Architecture; Cars; Digital photographs; Flowers; Riyadh, Saudi Arabia; Skyline; Streets/Roads
  - Street view of Al-Shuhada Street, National Bank of Kuwait (under construction), Kuwait., 12 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref29)
    Architecture; Cars; Construction; Digital photographs; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Men; Streets/Roads
  - Workers sitting along Jaber Al-Mubarak Street, Kuwait., 13 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref30)
    Cars; Digital photographs; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Men; Streets/Roads; Workers
  - View of Sheikh Zayed Road at Canal Kohr Cascades, Dubai., 14 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref31)
    Architecture; Cars; Digital photographs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Men; Streets/Roads; Women
  - Street view of The Opus Business Bay, Dubai., 14 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref32)
    Architecture; Cars; Digital photographs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Men; Streets/Roads
  - Carpark at Al-Shuhada Street, Kuwait., 11 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref33)
    Buildings; Cars; Digital photographs; Kuwait City, Kuwait
  - Carpark at Soor Street, Kuwait., 13 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref34)
  - View of Tamkeen Tower, Riyadh., 30 March 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref35)
    Buildings; Cars; Digital photographs; Riyadh, Saudi Arabia; Streets/Roads
  - KFC restaurant at Government Avenue, Manama., 14 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref36)
    Buildings; Cars; Digital photographs; Fountains; Manama, Bahrain; Restaurants
  - Street view of Al Muthana Avenue, Manama., 14 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref37)
    Buildings; Cars; Digital photographs; Manama, Bahrain; Streets/Roads
  - View of Business Bay, Dubai., 14 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref38)
    Buildings; Cars; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Women
  - Street view of Business Bay, Dubai., 13 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref39)
    Architecture; Buildings; Digital photographs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Skyline; Streets/Roads
  - Street view of Al Satwa Street, Dubai., 14 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref40)
    Cars; Digital photographs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Street lamps; Streets/Roads
  - View from Al Shuwaikh Beach, Kuwait., 12 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref41)
    Architecture; Beaches; Buildings; Digital photographs; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Skyline
  - View looking at Al Mariyah Island, Abu Dhabi., 18 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref42)
    Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Bicycles; Buildings; Digital photographs; Men; Skyline; Water
  - Night view from the Breakwater, Abu Dhabi., 16 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref43)
    Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Architecture; Lanterns/Lamps; Men; Skyline; Water
  - Night view of Dubai Marina Skyline from the Western tip of the Palm, Dubai., 12 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref44)
    Architecture; Digital photographs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Men; Skyline; Women
  - View from observatory of Burj Khalifa, Dubai., 14 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref45)
  - View at fountains at Mall of the Emirates, Dubai., 11 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref46)
    Buildings; Digital photographs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Fountains; Men; Women
  - Dubai Marina Creek, Dubai., 13 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref47)
    Architecture; Boats/Ships; Buildings; Digital photographs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Marina
  - View from beach at Dubai Marina, Dubai., 13 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref48)
    Architecture; Beaches; Buildings; Digital photographs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Water
  - Friday prayer at the Mosque of the Qatar Faculty of Islamic Studies, Doha., 17 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref49)
    Digital photographs; Doha, Qatar; Islamic Architecture; Mosques; Praying
  - View of skyline from the Corniche, Doha., 18 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref50)
    Architecture; Buildings; Corniche; Digital photographs; Doha, Qatar; Skyline
  - The Arch, Abu Dhabi., 17 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref51)
    Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Architecture; Digital photographs; Streets/Roads; Swimming Pools; Trees
  - Al Muneera, Abu Dhabi., 16 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref52)
    Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Buildings; Digital photographs; Skyline; Water
  - Al Bandar, Abu Dhabi., 16 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref53)
    Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Architecture; Boats/Ships; Buildings; Digital photographs
  - Al Reem Island, Abu Dhabi., 18 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref54)
    Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Architecture; Buildings; Cars; Construction; Streets/Roads
  - View over Sharq, Kuwait., 13 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref55)
    Architecture; Buildings; Digital photographs; Kuwait City, Kuwait
  - A view looking north along Al-Shuhada Street, Kuwait., 13 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref56)
    Architecture; Buildings; Cars; Digital photographs; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Streets/Roads
  - View from Al Reem Island, Abu Dhabi., 18 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref57)
    Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Architecture; Buildings; Digital photographs; Skyline
  - View from Al Shaheed Park, Kuwait., 12 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref58)
    Architecture; Buildings; Digital photographs; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Streets/Roads; Trees
  - View from travelators, looking for Dubai Mall, Dubai., 14 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref59)
    Digital photographs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Windows
  - View from Al Shaheed Park, Alfa Petrol, Kuwait., 12 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref60)
    Architecture; Buildings; Cars; Digital photographs; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Skyline; Street lamps; Streets/Roads
  - Fountains at The Opera House, Kuwait., 10 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref61)
    Buildings; Digital photographs; Fountains; Kuwait City, Kuwait; Water
  - View of King Fahad National Park, Riyadh., 27 March 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref62)
    Digital photographs; Fountains; Palm trees; Parks; Riyadh, Saudi Arabia; Skyline; Women
  - View from World Trade Center, Abu Dhabi., 18 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref63)
    Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Architecture; Digital photographs; Skyline; Windows
  - View from The Gate, Abu Dhabi., 17 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref64)
    Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Architecture; Buildings; Digital photographs; Skyline; Streets/Roads
  - View of The Gate, Abu Dhabi., 18 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref65)
    Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Architecture; Buildings; Cars; Digital photographs; Streets/Roads
  - Street view of Business Bay, Dubai., 14 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref66)
    Architecture; Buildings; Construction; Digital photographs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Men
  - View inside of Faculty of Islamic Studies, Doha., 17 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref67)
    Architecture; Digital photographs; Doha, Qatar; Islamic Architecture; Men
  - View of skyline from the Qatar Foundation Headquarters, Doha., 18 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref68)
    Architecture; Buildings; Digital photographs; Doha, Qatar; Skyline
  - North view of city from the Old Town, Doha., 18 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref69)
  - View of skyline from King Abdullah Financial District, Riyadh., 27 March 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref70)
    Architecture; Digital photographs; Riyadh, Saudi Arabia; Streets/Roads
  - Skyline of King Abdullah Financial District from Olaya street, Riyadh., 26 March 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref71)
    Architecture; Buildings; Construction; Digital photographs; Riyadh, Saudi Arabia; Skyline
  - Beach at Dubai Marina, Dubai., 13 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref72)
    Beaches; Buildings; Digital photographs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Men; Skyline; Women
  - Street view of King Abdullah Financial District under construction, Riyadh., 28 March 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref73)
    Buildings; Construction; Digital photographs; Riyadh, Saudi Arabia; Street signs; Streets/Roads
  - Interior of Qatar Foundation Headquarters, Doha., 16 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref74)
    Architecture; Buildings; Digital photographs; Doha, Qatar; Windows
  - Street view of bus stop at Palace Avenue, Manama., 14 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref75)
    Cars; Digital photographs; Manama, Bahrain; Street signs; Streets/Roads
  - Taxis in the Old Town of Doha, Doha., 18 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref76)
    Architecture; Digital photographs; Doha, Qatar; Men; Taxi
  - Kingdom Tower on King Fahad Road, Riyadh., 28 March 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref77)
  - Cascades at Canal Khor, Dubai., 13 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref78)
    Digital photographs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Men
  - South view of King Fahad Road, Riyadh., 29 March 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref79)
    Cars; Digital photographs; Riyadh, Saudi Arabia; Skyline; Street lamps; Streets/Roads
  - Night race at Yas Hotel, Abu Dhabi., 16 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref80)
    Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Cars; Digital photographs; Hotels; Street lamps
  - North view of King Fahad Road, Riyadh., 29 March 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref81)
    Buildings; Cars; Digital photographs; Riyadh, Saudi Arabia; Skyline; Street lamps; Streets/Roads
  - City skyline from near Manarat Al Sadiyaat, Abu Dhabi., 17 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref82)
  - View from Bahrain Bay, Manama., 14 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref83)
    Buildings; Digital photographs; Manama, Bahrain; Skyline; Water
  - View of skyline from beach at Al Ghous, Manama., 15 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref84)
    Beaches; Boats/Ships; Digital photographs; Manama, Bahrain; Skyline; Water
  - Skyline from the Breakwater, Abu Dhabi., 18 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref85)
    Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Cars; Digital photographs; Men; Skyline; Street lamps; Streets/Roads; Women
  - City view from skyline observation point, Doha., 15 Febrary 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref86)
    Architecture; Buildings; Digital photographs; Doha, Qatar; Men; Skyline
  - Street view of Isa Al Kabeer Avenue, Manama., 14 February 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref87)
    Architecture; Buildings; Cars; Digital photographs; Manama, Bahrain; Street signs; Streets/Roads
  - Aldar Headquarters, Abu Dhabi., 16 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref88)
    Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Architecture; Buildings; Digital photographs; Men
  - Ferrari World, Abu Dhabi., 16 January 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref89)
    Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Airplanes; Digital photographs; Parks
  - A can of Gulf Super glue, Riyadh., 27 March 2017; Nastasi, Michele, Mr (Object AD_MC_026_ref90)
    Digital photographs; Riyadh, Saudi Arabia